forex.com.pk 2015-06-14

# Privacy Statement of Forex.com.pk - Online Foreign Exchange Trading & Forex Rates in Pakistan

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at FOREX.com.pk. We take extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. 

Information Collection  
FOREX.com.pk and it's partner are the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not, or will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy statement below.

Advertisers:

  * We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. Google and other ad companies, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to **www.forex.com.pk**.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the website users based on their visit to **www.forex.com.pk** and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  * Third-party vendors and ad networks are also serving ads on this website. So cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on this site.
  * You may visit[ those websites](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) to opt out of cookies (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Log Files  
FOREX.com.pk keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's personal identification.

Sharing  
At this time, FOREX.com.pk does not share any information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.

Links  
Links to other sites outside of FOREX.com.pk do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to FOREX.com.pk. Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to FOREX.com.pk for information and data use for visitor's personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely to FOREX.com.pk.
